Kevin Baggott

Software Developer

Saint-Lazare, Quebec (438) 876-3622 kevin.baggott1@gmail.com

Languages: English (Native language), French (Intermediate)

ABOUT ME

I discovered my passion for coding in grade 6 while creating games with Scratch, a block-based programming language. Beyond programming, I have a keen interest in various sports, including golf and squash. I also dedicate at least 3 days a week into resistance training to stay fit and healthy. Additionally, I'm a motorcycle enthusiast with two years of riding experience and have admiration for all the different types of motorcycles.

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

Respectful, Patient, Honest, Dependable, Highly motivated with the ability to adapt quickly.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

C#, Python, JavaScript, Java, Bash, PowerShell, Kotlin, React, Express.js, Node.js, SQL, MongoDB, AutoSys Workload Automation, Dash, AG Grid

EXPERIENCE

Morgan Stanley, Montreal- Summer Intern

May 2023 - August 2023

- Front-End development of a web application.
- Technologies used: Python, Dash, AG Grid, AutoSys, React.

Bravo Pizzeria, Saint-Lazare- Delivery

June 2022 - PRESENT

- Delivering food.
- Making pizza boxes.

Walmart, Vaudreuil- eCommerce

April 2021 - October 2021

• Online orders department.

- Preparing orders and communicating with clients.
- General Labor.

Deville Technologies, Saint-Laurent- Receiving

June 2020 - August 2020

- Receiving Department (Responsible for department).
- General Labor.

Tim Hortons, Saint-Lazare- Clerk

June 2018 - May 2020

- Cash.
- Taking and serving customer orders.
- Sandwich bar.

EDUCATION

John Abbott College, Sainte-Anne-de-Bellevue- Computer Science

August 2021 - PRESENT

- Programming for applications, games and connected objects
- Problem Solving
- Security and Networking
- Database design
- Cloud computing

Course outlines or transcripts upon request

Westwood Senior High School, Hudson

August 2018 - June 2021

- Academic Honor Roll.
- Enrichment Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry.

Westwood Junior High School, Saint-Lazare

August 2016 - June 2018

- Academic Honor Roll.
- Matrix Enrichment Program.
- Robotics Club member.

Kevin Baggott

Développeur de Logiciels

Saint-Lazare, Quebec (438) 876-3622 kevin.baggott1@gmail.com

Langues: Anglais (Langue maternelle), Français (Intermédiaire)

À PROPOS DE MOI

J'ai découvert ma passion pour la programmation en sixième année en créant des jeux avec Scratch, un langage de programmation basé sur des blocs. Au-delà de la programmation, je m'intéresse à plusieurs sports, notamment le golf et le squash. Je consacre également au moins trois jours par semaine à l'entraînement en résistance pour rester en forme et en bonne santé. De plus, je suis un passionné de moto avec deux ans d'expérience de conduite et j'admire tous les différents types de motos.

QUALITÉS PERSONNELLES

Respectueux, patient, honnête, fiable, très motivé et capable de s'adapter rapidement.

COMPÉTENCES TECHNIQUES

C#, Python, JavaScript, Java, Bash, PowerShell, Kotlin, React, Express.js, Node.js, SQL, MongoDB, AutoSys Workload Automation, Dash, AG Grid

EXPÉRIENCE

Morgan Stanley, Montréal-Stagiaire d'été

Mai 2023 - Août 2023

- Développement Front-End d'une application web.
- Technologies utilisées: Python, Dash, AG Grid, AutoSys, React.

Bravo Pizzeria, Saint-Lazare- Livraison

Juin 2022 - PRÉSENT

- Livrer de la nourriture.
- Fabriquer des boîtes à pizza.

Avril 2021 - Octobre 2021

- Service de commandes en ligne.
- Préparer les commandes et communiquer avec les clients.
- Travail général.

Deville Technologies, Saint-Laurent- Receiving

Juin 2020 - Août 2020

- Département de réception (responsable du département).
- Travail général.

Tim Hortons, Saint-Lazare- Clerk

Juin 2018 - Mai 2020

- Caisse.
- Prendre et servir les commandes des clients.
- Bar à salade / sandwich.

ÉDUCATION

John Abbott College, Sainte-Anne-de-Bellevue- L'informatique

Août 2021 - PRÉSENT

- Programmation pour applications, jeux et objets connectés
- Résolution de problème
- Sécurité et Mise en Réseau
- Conception de base de données.
- Informatique en nuage

Plans de cours ou relevés de notes sur demande

Westwood Senior École Secondaire, Hudson

Août 2018 - Juin 2021

- Tableau d'honneur académique.
- Enrichissement Mathématiques, Physique et Chimie.

Westwood Junior École Secondaire, Saint-Lazare

Août 2016 - Juin 2018

- Tableau d'honneur académique.
- Programme d'enrichissement.
- Membre du Club de Robotique.